[{"answer": "That's it, I'm broke", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "That's it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "... Fine", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "... I'm sorry", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yo, my friend", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Whatta ya talkin' about it ain't my locker no more", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Twent", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah, they're goin',", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Spider Rice", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You think everybody I fight is a bum", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Don't get mental, man", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Ya always in a bad mood", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's right", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "The Bicentennial Heavyweight Championship of the World is gonna be held in the only place it can be held", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yo, Rock, you ain't happy with yourself?  Fine.  But me, I gotta business here", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend's sister", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " She ain't retarded, she's shy", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I don't need a doctor, I need a different job", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Do me a favor", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Looks quiet, y'know", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I think mebbe we're early or somethin'", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Look at her, ya can see she ain't feelin' good", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "... Ten minutes", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Few minutes", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Ten minutes for ten dollars", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "... I suppose", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It doesn't bother me either", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I know ya need sparrin' partners", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Absolutely", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Really think so", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Heart, but I ain't got no Tocker", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "The fight's set", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I got pain an' experience too", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " What's the attraction?  I don't see it", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What gaps", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What can I do about it", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What break?  Huh?  What break! Who am I to give breaks!  I'm a fighter, you haul meat.  You do what you do an' I do what I do best", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, I think any man who works an' trains hard always gotta chance", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'm always in shape", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "He's movin' to your left", "docId": "rocky.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Luck!  You fightin' a crazy man", "qsentId": 42}]